Fletcher School Records UA015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1930 -- 2002; UA015.001; 4.85 Linear Feet; 327 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher, 1955 -- 1962; UA015.001.005.00011 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    - Dean Robert B. Stewart sitting in a living room with seven people, 1962; UA015.001.005.00011.00006; E.M. Logan Studio (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
      Back: Lynne Khaishgi, unidentified, Kusuma Snitwongse, Sheikh Mujibur Rahman, Robert B. Stewart, S. Manjurhal H. Zaidi, K. Janaki, Tomoya Kawamura
      Graduate students; Deans; People; photographic print; Stewart, Robert B.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Students sitting with Professor Allan B. Cole, 1958; UA015.001.005.00011.00007; E.M. Logan Studio (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
      Left to right: Birabongse Kasemsri, unidentified, Allan B. Cole, S. Manjurhal H. Zaidi, Hiroshi Ohta, unidentified
      Graduate students; People; Professors; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Faculty and administrators eating at table, 1955; UA015.001.005.00011.00008; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
      Identified on the back: leftside- #2- Prof. R. J. Bartlett, #3- Savelle Davis, #4- Prof. Leo Gross, #5- Dr. Gregory Wolfe, #6- Prof. William Kelly; rightside- #1- VP Theodore Tredinnick, #2- Antony Cordozo, #3- Prof. Albert Imlah, #5- David Larson, #6- Prof. Norman Padelford
      People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
    - Fletcher students gathered around table in reading room, 1957; UA015.001.005.00011.00009; Duette Photographers (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
      Identified on the back: standing Giorgio Pagnonelli (Italy), Dean Hayden Williams (U.S.), Michael Obertin (Luxembourg); seated: Einar Benediktsson (Iceland), Joachim Luild (?) (Germany).
  - Group Photos: Awards, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00001 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Classrooms/meetings, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00002 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Commencement, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00003 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Field Trips, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00004 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Formal Events, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00005 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Informal Gatherings, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00006 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Library, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00007 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Lectures, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00008 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Professors' Offices, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00009 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Student Group Portraits, 1960; UA015.001.069.00010 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    - Fletcher students in stairwell, 1960; UA015.001.069.00010.00001; Hugh Rogers Photography (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
      People; Graduate students; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Group Photos: Visitors' Portraits, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00011 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Group Photos: Wilson House, Students, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00012 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Photo Proofs, Incomplete Photos, Unidentified, 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00013 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Unidentified Portraits (individuals), 1950 -- 1969; UA015.001.069.00014 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Class Photograph, 1947 -- 1948; UA015.001.069.00015 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    Folder includes identification of students in the photograph.
  - Group photos, 1950 -- 1965; UA015.001.069.00016 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    Photos received from the Ginn Library, Spring 2011. A small number of photos have some subjects identified.
  - Building photographs, 1950 -- 1965; UA015.001.069.00017 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    Photographs received from the Ginn Library, Spring 2011 (2011.111).
  - Professor Frank Nowak, 1950 -- 1965; UA015.001.069.00018 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - File Photos (Air Force) (Castro), 1975 -- 1980; UA015.001.069.00019 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
    Photographs received from the Ginn Library, Spring 2011 (2011.111). Includes NASA images, air force training in West Germany, and Castro in Ethiopia.
  - Secretary of State exhibit photos, 1984 -- 1989; UA015.001.069.00020 (Box data_value_missing_93e43fbac669414fc0b694e77938334a)
  - Richard B. Mancke, 1995; UA015.001.DO.03942; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    Richard B. Mancke, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Professor of International Economic Affairs (1974-1996) and Interim Dean (1994-1995).
    College administrators; Professors; photographic print; Mancke, Richard; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Harold Wilson, 1971; UA015.001.DO.03964; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 19)
    A second print is signed.
    Portraits; Faculty; photographic print; Wilson, Harold; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Professor Alfred P. Rubin at chalkboard (1), 1980; UA015.001.DO.04620; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Professors; Faculty; photographic print; Rubin, Alfred P.; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Dr. Barbara Burn, Professors Alan K. Henrikson and Igor Lukes, 1988; UA015.001.DO.04621; Sloan, J. D., 1946- (Box Shared 20)
    Professors; Events; Commencement; photographic print; Burn, Barbara; Henrikson, Alan; Lukes, Igor; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Professor Alfred P. Rubin at chalkboard (2), 1980; UA015.001.DO.04622; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Professor Michael Klein, 1998; UA015.001.DO.04861; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Image appeared in Fletcher School catalog, 1998, p. 16.
    Portraits; Professors; photographic print; Klein, Michael; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Professor Andrew Hess, 1983; UA015.001.DO.04863; Scott, Hillary S.L. (Box Shared 21)
    Photo taken summer, 1983.
    Portraits; Professors; photographic print; Hess, Andrew; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Fletcher students visit the United Nations, 1968; UA015.001.DO.04891; Rowen, George (Box Shared 22)
    People; Audiences; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
- General subject files, 1923 -- 1996; UA015.002; 2.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject files assembled by Russell Miller in his research for Light on the Hill. Most of the material dates between the 1920s and the 1960s, although some information from the 1980s is included. Correspondence accounts for the majority of the material. Materials include President Cousens' correspondence regarding the evolution of the school in the 1920s, and correspondence from Dean Hoskins, President Carmichael, and Vice President/Provost Mead. This series also includes files on special programs, such as the Latin American Teaching Fellowships, proposed curricular changes, "centers" within the school such as the Murrow Center, and special events. This series includes brochures and clippings. These files were left in the order established by Russell Miller.
  The materials in this series are grouped by document type and remain in the order created by Russell Miller.
  - Correspondence, planning, 1923 -- 1928; UA015.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Correspondence files from President John Cousens' files.
  - Correspondence, planning, 1929; UA015.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
    Correspondence from the files of President John Cousens.
  - Correspondence, planning, 1930 -- 1931; UA015.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, planning, 1932; UA015.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, planning, 1933; UA015.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, planning, 1934; UA015.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
    Corresondence from the files of President John Cousens.
  - Correspondence, 1935; UA015.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
    Correspondence files from the office of President John Cousens.
  - Correspondence, 1936; UA015.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
    Corresondence, primarily from the files of President Cousens; some from Dean Halford Hoskins' files.
  - Correspondence, 1937 -- 1938; UA015.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
    Correspondence from the files of the offices of Dean Halford Hoskins adn Presidents Cousens and Carmichael.
  - Correspondence, reports, 1939 -- 1941; UA015.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
    Correspondence from the office of Dean Halford Hoskins.
  - Correspondence, 1942 -- 1944; UA015.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, publications, 1945 -- 1953; UA015.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
    Correspondence from the files of Acting Dean Ruhl Bartlett, and Dean Robert B. Stewart
  - Correspondence, reports, 1955 -- 1960; UA015.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
    Materials from the office of Dean Robert Stewart
  - Correspondence, 1961 -- 1963; UA015.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
    Primarily correspondence from the files of Dean Robert Stewart.
  - Correspondence, reports, 1964 -- 1966; UA015.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
    Primarily correspondence from the office of Deans Robert Stewart and Edmund Gullion
  - Latin American reports, 1968 -- 1969; UA015.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
    Materials relating to a conference held in conjunction with the Latin American Teaching Fellows (LATF) program.
  - Correspondence, publications, reports, 1970 -- 1983; UA015.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Atlantic Community Program, 1962 -- 1964; UA015.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Curriculum, 1981; UA015.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Deanship, 1977; UA015.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - International business relations, 1979 -- 1981; UA015.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Joint advisory committee, 1935 -- 1942; UA015.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Opening, 1933; UA015.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - William L. Clayton lectures, 1957 -- 1984; UA015.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Announcements, bulletins, 1935 -- 1987; UA015.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Clippings, 1948 -- 1981; UA015.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Latin American Teaching Fellowships (1), 1974 -- 1978; UA015.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Latin American Teaching Fellowships (2), 1977; UA015.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Cabot Intercultural Center planning, 1976 -- 1979; UA015.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Cabot Intercultural Center, printed material, 1980 -- 1982; UA015.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Cabot Intercultural Center, correspondence, 1977 -- 1981; UA015.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Edward L. Bernays Foundation lecture, 1965 -- 1966; UA015.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Edward R. Murrow Center for Public Diplomacy, 1965 -- 1983; UA015.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, and brochures, 1975 -- 1996; UA015.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Poster for the opening of the Cabot Intercultural Center, 1981; UA015.002.010.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case.
- Dean's office correspondence, 1934 -- 1981; 1950 -- 1970; UA015.003; 6.05 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence files from the office of the Dean of the Fletcher School. Correspondence from Deans Gullion and Stewart are included in this series. The bulk of these materials are from 1950 to 1970. These files were received in alphabetical order by correspondent, and this order has been maintained.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - A - Dean Robert B. Stewart, Part 1 of 2 (Ac-Ah), 1945 -- 1965; UA015.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - A - Dean Robert B. Stewart, part 2 of 2 (Al-Az), 1946 -- 1963; UA015.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence (Gullion), Ab-As, 1964 -- 1979; UA015.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Ba-Br, 1957 -- 1967; UA015.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence (Gullion), Ba, 1964 -- 1974; UA015.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence (Gullion), Ba-Bl, 1964 -- 1971; UA015.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Blum, Jonathan, 1972 -- 1973; UA015.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Bl-Br, 1948 -- 1970; UA015.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Bu, 1964 -- 1975; UA015.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - (Mrs.) Hamilton J. Baker, 1952 -- 1962; UA015.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - George Ball, 1965 -- 1968; UA015.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Andrew Berding, 1948 -- 1962; UA015.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - William W. Bishop, 1947 -- 1960; UA015.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Eugene R. Black, 1960 -- 1966; UA015.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Thomas C. Blaisdell, Jr., 1947 -- 1958; UA015.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Lincoln Bloomfield, 1950 -- 1971; UA015.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Harry Blotner, 1948 -- 1966; UA015.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Richard L. Bowditch, 1953 -- 1959; UA015.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Ralph J. Bunche, 1945 -- 1972; UA015.003.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - McGeorge Bundy, 1953 -- 1965; UA015.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - William Bundy, 1963 -- 1970; UA015.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Vannevar Bush, 1948 -- 1959; UA015.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Ca-Cl, 1960 -- 1973; UA015.003.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Co-Cu, part 1 of 2 (Ca-Cr), 1946 -- 1980; UA015.003.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Co-Cu, part 2 of 2 (Cr-Cu), 1946 -- 1971; UA015.003.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Godfrey L. Cabot, 1945 -- 1963; UA015.003.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Louis W. Cabot, 1961 -- 1980; UA015.003.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Judy Cabot, 1962 -- 1970; UA015.003.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Leonard Carmichael, 1950 -- 1971; UA015.003.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - George A. Carroll, 1964 -- 1967; UA015.003.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Mohamed Ali Currim Chagla, 1958 -- 1959; UA015.003.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - William L. Clayton, 1962 -- 1966; UA015.003.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Harlan Cleveland, 1952 -- 1974; UA015.003.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Yale Cooper, 1962 -- 1969; UA015.003.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Dean Z. Cowen, 1953 -- 1964; UA015.003.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - Prescott C. Crafts, Jr., 1959 -- 1981; UA015.003.011.00036 (Box 11)
    The tab on the hanging file in which this materials were originally housed also contained the note: "See also: International Trade Center of New England"
  - Dr. Ivan C. Crawford, 1947 -- 1962; UA015.003.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - John F. Crawford, 1965, UA015.003.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - Dean's office correspondence, Da, 1947 -- 1973; UA015.003.011.00039 (Box 11)
    These materials were found loose in a hanging file with the tab title, "Da-De" (other materials in this hanging file were separated into manila folders and are found in folders 11:40 and 11:41).
  - Darvall, 1968 -- 1970; UA015.003.011.00040 (Box 11)
    Originally housed in a manila file in a hanging file with the tab title, "Da-De."
  - Shelby Cullom Davis, 1971 -- 1980; UA015.003.011.00041 (Box 11)
    Originally housed in a manila file in a hanging folder with the tab title "Da-De."
  - Dean's office correspondence, Da-De, 1959 -- 1973; UA015.003.011.00042 (Box 11)
    These materials were found loose in a hanging file with the tab title "Da-De." Other materials were housed in manila folders and may be found in folders 11:40 and 11:41.
  - Di-Du, 1965 -- 1976; UA015.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Nathaniel Davis, 1961 -- 1965; UA015.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Saville R. Davis, 1946 -- 1963; UA015.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Karl W. Deutsch, 1957 -- 1963; UA015.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Ea-Es, 1947 -- 1977; UA015.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - F, part 1, 1949 -- 1970; UA015.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - F, part 2, 1952 -- 1976; UA015.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - John K. Fairbank, 1948 -- 1959; UA015.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Dante B. Fascell, 1966 -- 1977; UA015.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Carl J. Freidrich, 1946 -- 1962; UA015.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Ga-Go, part 1, 1962 -- 1973; UA015.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Ga-Go, part 2, 1952 -- 1973; UA015.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Gr-, 1962 -- 1975; UA015.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Erwin N. Griswold, 1947 -- 1965; UA015.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Lincoln Gordon, 1949 -- 1966; UA015.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Andrew Gyorgy, 1953 -- 1956; UA015.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Ha, part 1, 1964 -- 1974; UA015.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Ha, part 2, 1961 -- 1971; UA015.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - He, 1957 -- 1975; UA015.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Hi, part 1, 1959 -- 1976; UA015.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Hi, part 2, 1947 -- 1973; UA015.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Hi, part 3, 1958 -- 1971; UA015.003.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Louis J. Halle, part 1, 1974 -- 1981; UA015.003.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Louis J. Halle, part 2, 1965 -- 1974; UA015.003.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Louis J. Halle, part 3, 1967; UA015.003.012.00025 (Box 12)
    Date is approximate
  - Abraham M. Halpern, 1965; UA015.003.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Averell W. Harriman, 1958 -- 1971; UA015.003.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Parker T. Hart, 1969; UA015.003.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Denis Healey, 1949 -- 1966; UA015.003.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - Robert W. Hill, 1949 -- 1962; UA015.003.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - Roger Hilsman, 1958 -- 1966; UA015.003.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - I, 1963 -- 1973; UA015.003.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - J, 1963 -- 1973; UA015.003.012.00033 (Box 12)
  - Lady Barbara W. Jackson, 1947 -- 1962; UA015.003.012.00034 (Box 12)
  - Philip C. Jessup, 1946 -- 1964; UA015.003.012.00035 (Box 12)
  - K, part 1, 1961 -- 1972; UA015.003.012.00036 (Box 12)
  - K, part 2, 1961 -- 1972; UA015.003.012.00037 (Box 12)
  - James H. Keeley, 1950 -- 1976; UA015.003.012.00038 (Box 12)
  - Hans Kelsen, 1950 -- 1956; UA015.003.012.00039 (Box 12)
  - George F. Kennan, 1951 -- 1971; UA015.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - John F. Kennedy, 1953 -- 1972; UA015.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - John F. Kennedy, 1946 -- 1964; UA015.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Robert Kennedy, 1966 -- 1967; UA015.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Henry A. Kissinger, 1952 -- 1976; UA015.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Harry L. Kingman, 1965 -- 1966; UA015.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Kurt Georg Kiesinger, 1966 -- 1967; UA015.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Tracy B. Kittredge, 1956 -- 1971; UA015.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Tracy B. Kittredge, 1946 -- 1961; UA015.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Josef Korbel, 1952 -- 1963; UA015.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - L, part 1, 1957 -- 1976; UA015.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - L, part 2, 1956 -- 1976; UA015.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - John M. Leddy, 1950 -- 1964; UA015.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Priscilla Lee, 1953; UA015.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Edna Fuerth Lemle, 1969 -- 1970; UA015.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - James L. Ling, 1966 -- 1970; UA015.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Ronald T. Lyman, Jr., 1960 -- 1978; UA015.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Mac and Mc, 1961 -- 1976; UA015.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - George C. McGhee, 1949 -- 1968; UA015.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Ma-Me, part 1, 1962 -- 1969; UA015.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Ma-Me, part 2, UA015.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Ma-Me, 1962 -- 1973; UA015.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Mi, 1955 -- 1974; UA015.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Charles H. Malik, 1959 -- 1962; UA015.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - John W. Masland, 1946 -- 1963; UA015.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - Edward C. Mason, 1949 -- 1963; UA015.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - G.L. Mehta, 1952 -- 1963; UA015.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - Hans J. Morgenthau, 1957 -- 1959; UA015.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Archie T. Morrison, 1961 -- 1966; UA015.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
  - Bradford Morse, 1969 -- 1976; UA015.003.013.00030 (Box 13)
  - Mugar Family, 1966 -- 1979; UA015.003.013.00031 (Box 13)
  - Robert Murphy, 1966 -- 1970; UA015.003.013.00032 (Box 13)
  - Edmund S. Muskie, 1970 -- 1971; UA015.003.013.00033 (Box 13)
  - Denys P. Myers, 1945 -- 1964; UA015.003.013.00034 (Box 13)
  - Na-Ne, 1945 -- 1969; UA015.003.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Ni, 1960 -- 1975; UA015.003.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Earl Newsom, 1958 -- 1964; UA015.003.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Richard Nixon, 1968 -- 1972; UA015.003.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - O, 1959 -- 1971; UA015.003.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Pa-Ph, 1951 -- 1979; UA015.003.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Norman J. Pedelford, 1951 -- 1979; UA015.003.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Pi, 1958 -- 1975; UA015.003.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Ross Perot, 1970 -- 1971; UA015.003.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - John N. Plank, 1962 -- 1965; UA015.003.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Q, 1952 -- 1965; UA015.003.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Ra-Ri, 1959 -- 1976; UA015.003.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Ro-, 1962 -- 1976; UA015.003.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Jacques J. Reinstein, 1963 -- 1969; UA015.003.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - David Rockefeller, 1962 -- 1963; UA015.003.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1949 -- 1961; UA015.003.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Walt Rostow, 1968 -- 1972; UA015.003.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Dean Rusk, part 1, 1964 -- 1973; UA015.003.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Dean Rusk, part 2, 1963 -- 1967; UA015.003.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Sa-Sc, 1962 -- 1975; UA015.003.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Se-Si, 1958 -- 1974; UA015.003.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Sk-, 1969 -- 1977; UA015.003.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - S, part 1, 1960 -- 1967; UA015.003.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - S, part 2, 1957 -- 1968; UA015.003.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Hans H. Sante, 1969 -- 1974; UA015.003.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Raymond J. Saulnier, 1961 -- 1962; UA015.003.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - J. Robert Schaetzel, 1962 -- 1964; UA015.003.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Edgar von Schmidt-Pauli, 1967; UA015.003.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Philipp Schmidt-Schlegel, 1961 -- 1964; UA015.003.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - David Schwartz, 1962 -- 1976; UA015.003.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Sargent Shriver, 1964 -- 1975; UA015.003.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Louis B. John, 1948 -- 1963; UA015.003.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Joseph P. Spang, 1966; UA015.003.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Eugene Staley, 1944 -- 1960; UA015.003.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - George P. Steiger, 1948 -- 1950; UA015.003.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - LeRoy Stinebower, 1946 -- 1954; UA015.003.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Julius Stone, Part 1, 1949 -- 1964; UA015.003.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Julius Stone, part 2, 1934 -- 1948; UA015.003.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Ta-Th, 1962 -- 1977; UA015.003.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Ti-, 1965 -- 1975; UA015.003.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Grace Trefrey, 1961 -- 1969; UA015.003.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Willard L. Thorp, 1950 -- 1965; UA015.003.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - George O. Totten, 1953 -- 1965; UA015.003.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Max Tischler, 1961 -- 1973; UA015.003.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - U, 1953 -- 1972; UA015.003.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Nobushige Ukai, 1960 -- 1961; UA015.003.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - V, 1960 -- 1973; UA015.003.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Richard W. Van Alstyne, 1949 -- 1950; UA015.003.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Wa-We, 1960 -- 1971; UA015.003.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Wa-We, 1963 -- 1973; UA015.003.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Wo-, 1948 -- 1971; UA015.003.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Wh-Wi, 1952 -- 1974; UA015.003.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Frances O. Wilson, 1945 -- 1959; UA015.003.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - David M. Wilson, 1964 -- 1968; UA015.003.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - George H. Wittman, 1972 -- 1973; UA015.003.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - George H. Wittman, 1968 -- 1972; UA015.003.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Martha S. Woolley, 1953 -- 1957; UA015.003.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Adm., Joseph Wylie, 1970 -- 1973; UA015.003.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - X-Z, 1961 -- 1974; UA015.003.017.00003 (Box 17)
- Dean's office subject files, 1938 -- 1990; 1960 -- 1976; UA015.004; 17.05 Linear Feet